e-gmat.com 2018-10-05

# privacy policy - e-GMAT

## Privacy Policy

“GMAT” and other GMAC™ trademarks are registered trademarks of the Graduate Management Admission Council™. The Graduate Management Admission Council™ does not endorse, nor is affiliated in any way with YourPerfectScore or www.e-gmat.com. The content and the opinions expressed on www.e-gmat.com belong solely to the employees and users of www.e-gmat.com.  
E-GMAT and YourPerfectScore (together referred as YPS going forward in this agreement) are committed to protecting their privacy. Please continue to use the privacy policy below for more details. Please be sure to read our [terms and conditions](https://e-gmat.com/terms-and-conditions/) section in conjunction with the privacy policy as well. This privacy policy together with the terms and conditions constitutes the entire agreement between you and YPS. By registering on the website, you agree to abide by the entire agreement.

#### 1\. PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

To provide services we collect certain personal information to be able to provide services to users. This information includes but not limited to name, date of birth, email address and credit card number. In additional we may collect certain information that cannot be used to identify a user but is collected to statistical purposes such as demographic information, the average time that a user spends on the website etc. Such information that does not uniquely identity a particular user may be shared with our partners, affiliates, sponsors, and other third parties.  
Registered User may be provided a unique username and password that enable access to the Service. We may track the use of those usernames and passwords in order to collect and maintain records of individual transactions conducted through the Services by Registered Users, and those records may be associated with each Registered User’s individual account profile within the Company system.  
Please note that you may not divulge your account information (username/password) to anyone. Under no circumstances would we ask for your password via e mail. If you have any further question, please contact support@e-gmat.com

#### 2\. Use of Personal Information

YPS uses personal information for the following purposes:  
1\. To identify you to provide access to the account.  
2\. To maintain your account and to improve the quality of services provided to you by customizing our services as per your preferences.  
3\. To promote and market product and services offered by YPS, its partners and its associates.  
4\. To bill you for the products and services.  
YPS will not sell or lease your personal information to third-parties. If YPS is sold, your personal information is one of the assets that would be transferred by YPS.

#### 3\. COOKIES

From time to time YPS may place a cookie on your computer. A “cookie” is a small line of code that is stored in your browser when you visit a cookie-enabled website. A cookie allows us to track and keep records on user activity. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you set your browser to reject cookies, it is possible that some parts of the Website will not function. Moreover, in order to use the Services, your browser must accept cookies.

#### 4\. DISCLOSURE FOR LAW ENFORCEMENT PURPOSES

The information provided by you is not shared with any third parties and resides only with officers of YPS. However, under certain circumstances, we may be subject to legal requirements by a government agency to disclose personal information. YPS intends to fully comply with all such requirements. If you do not want us to make these necessary disclosures please do not use these service

#### 5\. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

YPS reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Please review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you are up to date with the latest terms. Please contact legal@e-gmat.com, if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy..  
© 2010 YourPerfectScore, LLC All Rights Reserved.
